1keydata.com 2017-06-26

# 1Keydata Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy for 1keydata.com

The privacy of our visitors to 1keydata.com is important to us. 

At 1keydata.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit 1keydata.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We use third party advertisements on 1keydata.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

DoubleClick DART Cookies 

We may use the Google Adsense program on our pages. Google uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on visitor's web browsing history. Visitors may opt out of the user of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.   

* * *

Copyright 2016   1keydata.com   All Rights Reserved     Privacy Policy   About   Contact
